<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>commissions on Math the Printer</title>
    <link>https://maththeprinter.github.io/tags/commissions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in commissions on Math the Printer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://maththeprinter.github.io/tags/commissions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The beer bottles of Brasserie Artisanale Autre Monde</title>
      <link>https://maththeprinter.github.io/thornwood-copie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maththeprinter.github.io/thornwood-copie/</guid>
      <description>The beer bottles of Brasserie Artisanale Autre Monde These illustrations were made as a commission for a french Brewery. You can see the creatures on display on their beer bottles on their website as well http://brasserieautremonde.fr/
The creative process This commissioned work has taken place in 2022, and as one of my personal projects, it took me way more than necessary because i wanted it to be perfect. From the choice of the paper, to the illustration itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thornwood Parfums</title>
      <link>https://maththeprinter.github.io/thornwood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maththeprinter.github.io/thornwood/</guid>
      <description>Thornwood Parfums This project was a commission from a NZ brand in the fragrance game. They wanted to develop a strong artwork line, invoking the heavy designs from the gothic medieval era, that i love and try to put forward.
Thornwood wanted 5 woodcuts that evoked a specific mind state. Just as if you could describe an olfactive impression with words. Difficult, innit? Well i did exactly that with feelings and linocut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Of Thrones Fan art &#39;#1</title>
      <link>https://maththeprinter.github.io/game-of-thrones-fan-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maththeprinter.github.io/game-of-thrones-fan-art/</guid>
      <description>The technique The sketch was originally drawn on transparent paper, then reported on the lino block, then inked with on the block. Once dried out, the block was carved with gouges: the linocut process itself. This process was particularly long, due to the massive amount of texts that is included in the orginal poem.
This was one of my earliest projects, one of my biggest occasions to learn and do mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
