<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>archive on Math the Printer</title>
    <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/tags/archive/</link>
    <description>Recent content in archive on Math the Printer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://MathThePrinter.github.io/tags/archive/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Sweet Zombie Jesus</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/sweet-zombie-jesus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/sweet-zombie-jesus/</guid>
      <description>Sweet Zombie Jesus This illustration was done under an hour in Krita
This was made out of fun, between 2 and 3 AM instead of going to bed. Every late night drawing begins with &amp;ldquo;C&amp;rsquo;mon, just one last bit&amp;rdquo;. And ends up way to late.
Technique The technique used was, as i like to call it &amp;ldquo;Digital carving &amp;quot; technique. This consists in several succssive steps
Sketching using a pencil brush Put a black layer on top, in high opacity to distinguish the sketch through the canvas With a white brush, or on erasing mode, withdraw the black from the canvas to create the whites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chimera</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/chimere/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/chimere/</guid>
      <description>The Chimera (🇫🇷 La Chimère) This illustration was made as a commission for a french Brewery. You can see the creatures on display on their beer bottles on their website http://brasserieautremonde.fr/ The brewery only displays the illustrations in black and white, and the colored version are more a proof of concept of coloring my own digital art.
Technique The technique used was, as i like to call it &amp;ldquo;Digital carving &amp;quot; technique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Faun</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/faune/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/faune/</guid>
      <description>The Faun (🇫🇷 Le Faune) This illustration was made as a commission for a french Brewery. You can see the creatures on display on their beer bottles on their website http://brasserieautremonde.fr/ The brewery only displays the illustrations in black and white, and the colored version are more a proof of concept of coloring my own digital art.
Technique The technique used was, as i like to call it &amp;ldquo;Digital carving &amp;quot; technique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Griffin</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/griffon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/griffon/</guid>
      <description>The Griffin (🇫🇷 Le Griffon) This illustration was made as a commission for a french Brewery. You can see the creatures on display on their beer bottles on their website http://brasserieautremonde.fr/ The brewery only displays the illustrations in black and white, and the colored version are more a proof of concept of coloring my own digital art.
Technique The technique used was, as i like to call it &amp;ldquo;Digital carving &amp;quot; technique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Minotaur</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/minotaure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/minotaure/</guid>
      <description>The Minotaur (🇫🇷 Le Minotaure) This illustration was made as a commission for a french Brewery. You can see the creatures on display on their beer bottles on their website http://brasserieautremonde.fr/ The brewery only displays the illustrations in black and white, and the colored version are more a proof of concept of coloring my own digital art.
Technique The technique used was, as i like to call it &amp;ldquo;Digital carving &amp;quot; technique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wolpertinger</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/wolpert/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/wolpert/</guid>
      <description>The Wolpertinger (🇫🇷 Le Wolpertinger) This illustration was made as a commission for a french Brewery. You can see the creatures on display on their beer bottles on their website http://brasserieautremonde.fr/ The brewery only displays the illustrations in black and white, and the colored version are more a proof of concept of coloring my own digital art.
Technique The technique used was, as i like to call it &amp;ldquo;Digital carving &amp;quot; technique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hog</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/the-hog/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/the-hog/</guid>
      <description>The Hog This is an original artwork freely inspired by modern linocuts. Stepping aside from my usual renaissance inspired artworks, i decided to take a shot at a modern design.
The scene represents a wounded hog, pierced by several arrows. The main thing about this linocut was to nail the fur, and the shading of the hairs.
The techniques The sketch was directly drawn on the lino block, then inked with a quill on the block.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anakin and the Order 66, as seen from the XVIth century</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/order-66/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/order-66/</guid>
      <description>Anakin and the Order 66 This is an original artwork freely inspired by the XVI century woodcuts. The graphic style tends to imitate the master woodcutters (Dürer, Egenolff, Wolgemut) of the late XVth century, early XVIth , both in terms of tools, techniques, and the posture and symbolism itself.
The scene represents Anakin Skywalker wearing a XVIth century milanese armor, during the order 66. The two suns of tattooine are shining over a scorched earth, on which the Jedi banner is burning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astartes with a flamethrower</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/ultramarine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/ultramarine/</guid>
      <description>Technique The technique used was, as i like to call it &amp;ldquo;Digital carving &amp;quot; technique. This consists in several succssive steps
Sketching using a pencil brush Put a black layer on top, in high opacity to distinguish the sketch through the canvas With a white brush, or on erasing mode, withdraw the black from the canvas to create the whites. The colors were added on a separate layer on top, with the multiply blending mode on </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Buffalunicorn</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/bufflicorne/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/bufflicorne/</guid>
      <description>The Allmighty Buffallunicorn (🇫🇷 Bufflicorne) This illustration was done under an hour in Krita
This was made out of fun, between 2 and 3 AM instead of going to bed. Every late night drawing begins with &amp;ldquo;C&amp;rsquo;mon, just one last bit&amp;rdquo;. And ends up way to late.
Technique The technique used was, as i like to call it &amp;ldquo;Digital carving &amp;quot; technique. This consists in several succssive steps
Sketching using a pencil brush Put a black layer on top, in high opacity to distinguish the sketch through the canvas With a white brush, or on erasing mode, withdraw the black from the canvas to create the whites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Landsknecht on the field</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/landsknecht-on-the-field-copy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/landsknecht-on-the-field-copy/</guid>
      <description>The Landsknecht This is an original artwork freely inspired by the XVI century woodcuts. The graphic style tends to imitate the master woodcutters (Dürer, Egenolff, Wolgemut) of the late XVth century, early XVIth , both in terms of tools, techniques, and the posture and symbolism itself.
The scene represents a Landsknecht wearing a XVIth century costume, as seen on imagery (woodcuts, paintings, drawings), from that period of time. This print is a part of a tryptich concerning 3 warriors : a dwarf, a goblin and a human, all three wearing XVIth century war gear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mounted dwarf</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/nain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/nain/</guid>
      <description>Technique The technique used was, as i like to call it &amp;ldquo;Digital carving &amp;quot; technique. This consists in several succssive steps
Sketching using a pencil brush Put a black layer on top, in high opacity to distinguish the sketch through the canvas With a white brush, or on erasing mode, withdraw the black from the canvas to create the whites. The colors were added on a separate layer on top, with the multiply blending mode on </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Duellists</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/duellists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/duellists/</guid>
      <description>The Duellists This is an original artwork freely inspired by the XVI century woodcuts. The graphic style tends to imitate the master woodcutters (Dürer, Egenolff, Wolgemut) of the late XVth century, early XVIth , both in terms of tools, techniques, and the posture and symbolism itself.
The scene represents two swordplayers wearing XVIth century costume, and fighting using longswords, as seen on renaissance treatises and codices from that period of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Goblin landsknecht</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/goblin-landsknecht/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/goblin-landsknecht/</guid>
      <description>The Goblin landsknecht This is an original artwork freely inspired by the XVI century woodcuts. The graphic style tends to imitate the master woodcutters (Dürer, Egenolff, Wolgemut) of the late XVth century, early XVIth , both in terms of tools, techniques, and the posture and symbolism itself.
The scene represents a Goblin Landsknecht wearing a XVIth century costume, as seen on imagery (woodcuts, paintings, drawings), from that period of time. Though there is little information regarding goblin folk at this era, the costume field itself is pretty well documented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thornwood Parfums</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/thornwood/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/thornwood/</guid>
      <description>Thornwood Parfums This project was a commission from a NZ brand in the fragrance game. They wanted to develop a strong artwork line, invoking the heavy designs from the gothic medieval era, that i love and try to put forward.
Thornwood wanted 5 woodcuts that evoked a specific mind state. Just as if you could describe an olfactive impression with words. Difficult, innit? Well i did exactly that with feelings and linocut.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Dreadnought and the Ork boss</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/dreadnought/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/dreadnought/</guid>
      <description>Brother Saint Georges in a Dreadnought, fighting with Big Boss Drakka da Dragon 2021, not colorised.
I always loved greenskins and history. And when i had the chance to create an artwork that could use both my passions, i jumped on it.
This project was the right occasion to try to tighten the bonds between a medieval motif and a modern approach of it. I wanted to go for the religious effect on the render, as were the woodcuts from the gothic medieval era, at the very first years of XVIth century</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dwarven Brewery</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/the-dwarven-brewery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/the-dwarven-brewery/</guid>
      <description>The Dwarwen Brewery This fantastic representation of a dwarven colony-sized booze frenzy was inspired by a XIIIth treatise on beer brewing [available here] This linocut depicts a dwarven brewery, a personal view of this poem.
Mainly because I like dwarves and i think the fantasy kind of dwarf encapsulates perfectly the light spirit that i thought might correspond to this XIIIth brewery. This contains the original verses in old french, describing all the malting and brewing process, to the final step of getting hammered and wanting to forget about it all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game Of Thrones Fan art &#39;#1</title>
      <link>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/game-of-thrones-fan-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://MathThePrinter.github.io/game-of-thrones-fan-art/</guid>
      <description>The technique The sketch was originally drawn on transparent paper, then reported on the lino block, then inked with on the block. Once dried out, the block was carved with gouges: the linocut process itself. This process was particularly long, due to the massive amount of texts that is included in the orginal poem.
This was one of my earliest projects, one of my biggest occasions to learn and do mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
